伍德布里奇的紧张形势终于趋于缓和
Tensions have cooled here at Woodbridge,
但就在几晚之前 校园因为一本叫做
but just a few nights ago, the campus was in flames
《风骚女子》的色情女性杂志陷入一片火海
over a new pornographic ladies' magazine called "Minx."
这份内容活泼的印刷物
Copies of the frisky periodical
风靡校园 引发了一场激烈辩论
blew through the quad, igniting a raucous debate
也引起了当地人的愤慨
that has left locals raging.
这种事情发生在私校 成何体统
They're called privates for a reason.
这是媒体产业放大主流女权主义
This is yet another example of the media industrial complex
声音的又一例证
amplifying the voices of mainstream feminists.
女孩若看来这个就会想做爱吗
Reading this is supposed to make girls want sex?
我不懂
I don't get it.
地方已经成立了行动小组
Local action groups have already formed
来抗议这本杂志
to protest the magazine.
这种脏东西绝不能出现在我们社区
This filth has no place in our community.
我会跟恩西诺的热心群众一道
I stand with the concerned citizens of Encino,
在正派 敬畏上帝的人们的帮助下
decent, God-fearing people who will help us win the fight
赢得圣费尔南多谷的灵魂保卫战
for the soul of the San Fernando Valley.
好了 加油
Okay, okay.
坚持下去 不要停
Keep it up. Keep it up.
我要打印底片 我可以
I have negatives to print. Can I just--
少说 多舔
Less talkin', more lickin'.
这话放以前我可爱听了
I used to love hearing that.
再来几个信封
More envelopes, please.
没错
There you go.
《查兹沃斯的贞操捍卫者》很好
"Champions of Chatsworth Chastity"-- good.
《范奈斯镇的处女义警》
"Virgin Vigilantes of Van Nuys."
-我都读不下来  -没人读得下来
- I can't even say that one. - No one can.
所以上了新闻才那么搞笑
That's why it's gonna be so funny on the news.
这份是我的大作
This one's my masterpiece.
《好莱坞山的关切主妇》
"Heavy-Hearted Housewives of Hollywood Hills."
看 还押了头韵
They call that alliteration.
你在整我 这招我太熟了
Okay, you're fucking with me. I know this move.
听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我使劲浑身解数 要力挽狂澜
I'm trying to pull a rabbit out of a hat here.
你能帮帮我吗
Could you please help me?
不错 《穆赫兰的端庄魔术师》
Ooh, "Matronly Magicians of Mulholland."
我真受不了爸爸妈妈吵架
I hate it when Mom and Dad fight.
所以这些团体都不存在
Wait, so none of these groups are real?
道格 能聊聊吗
Doug, may I have a word, please?
这是我的专长
Let me do my job.
起作用了 我在改天换日 撼动大局
It's working. I'm moving. I'm shaking.
把水搅混 大家议论纷纷
I'm stirring the pot. People are talking.
对 但都是批评的声音
Yeah, but it's all criticism.
如果大家都喜欢 那就没有话题性了
If everybody was loving it, we wouldn't have a story.
乔伊斯 各路记者都快打爆我电话了
Joyce, I got reporters calling me from everywhere--
有《旧金山纪事报》的
from the "San Francisco Chronicle,"
有《费城问询报》的
from the "Philadelphia Inquirer."
-都是小报  -但起作用了
- That's a lesser paper. - It's working.
你第二期的内容做得非常完美
And you did a killer job stepping up issue two.
里奇的那个封面
And Richie's cover?
性感爆棚了
Very sexy stuff, Joyce.
没错
Yes!
看看来了多少根屌
Look at how many more dicks you got.
你应该为这本
- Mm-hmm. - You should be so proud
出色的杂志骄傲
of this excellent magazine.
一本出色的杂志 如果被所有人误读
Yeah, but what's the point of making it excellent
又有什么意义呢
if everybody's reading it the wrong way?
你什么意思 难不成他们读反了
What do you mean by that? You mean, like, back to front?
我想让女性觉得力量满满 而不是羞辱连连
I want women to feel empowered, not embarrassed.
-我得跟这些记者聊聊  -不要 绝对不行
- Let me talk to these reporters. - Oh, no, no, not a chance.
这个计划好不容易奏效 你会坏了我的好事
The plan is working. You'll just Joyce it up.
这么做会吓跑我们的目标读者的
We are scaring away our target audience.
好吧 这样吧
Just-- all right, you know what?
我分给你一个记者
I'll give you one reporter.
我天 你可真大方
Oh, my God, you're so generous.
无聊 刻薄
Okay, stuffy. Mean.
出了名的贪婪
Notoriously grabby.
贝乌拉·巴雷特也打给你了
Beulah Barrett called?
她特别擅长为陷入危机的名人写专题
She does the best profiles on celebrities in crisis.
-我成名人了  -对 你就是名人
- Am I a celebrity? - Sure, you're a celebrity.
来 给我吧 你可以跟他们讲讲
Here, give them to me. Tell them your vision
-你对第二期的宏伟愿景  -好
for issue two. - Yeah.
你还可以这么做
And then why don't you do this?
你还可以
Why don't you, uh...
教她们如何阅读这本杂志
teach them how they should read it?
拿起黄色记号笔 保持一颗开放的心
With a yellow highlighter and an open heart.
上帝保佑丁丁女王
奇怪 竟然把这个忘了
Oh, how funny. We missed this one.
让我
Let me just, uh...
等等 是给我的
ah, but wait, it's for me.
所有巧合都是精心安排
There are no coincidences.
这是毛主席教给我的
Chairman Mao taught me that.
亲爱的里奇 我有注意到你在《风骚女子》中的作品
"Dear Richie, noticed your work in 'Minx.'
有空来坐坐 我们聊聊
Come see us sometime. Let's chat."
爱德华·肖恩 来自爱德华·肖恩画廊
Edward Shawn of the Edward Shawn Gallery.
天啊 他有两个名字
Oh, my God, he has two first names.
-好高级啊  -是啊
- That's so fancy. - I know.
他拥有西好莱坞最时髦的画廊
He has the chicest gallery in West Hollywood
还有一双识才慧眼
and a real eye for emerging artists.
他教会了大卫·霍克尼游泳
He taught David Hockney how to swim.
天 他不会是想展示你的作品吧
Wow. What if he wants to show your photos?
或者想和你做爱
Or what if he wants to have sex with you?
-也许两者皆有  -这上面只说了聊聊
- Sometimes it's both. - Mm, just says chat.
周围的小伙伴终于得到了
I am so glad someone is finally getting
应有的认可 我好开心
the recognition they deserve around here.
是啊
Yes, well,
等我哪一天我出名了
whenever it happens for me and I become famous,
我保证咱们的友谊不会变
I promise we'll still be friends.
我已经很出名了 所以我懂你意思
I'm already famous, so I understand.
普利格女士
Ms. Prigger?
我是美联社的特伦斯·卡朋特
Terrence Carpenter, "Associated Press."
不是说好了贝乌拉吗
Uh, what happened to Beulah?
她跟克罗莉丝·李奇曼
Last-minute emergency sit-down
有个紧急会面
with Cloris Leachman.
你懂的
You understand.
哦 对 当然
Oh, yeah, of course.
克罗莉丝·李奇曼（1926年4月30日-2021年1月27日）是美国女演员和喜剧演员
克罗莉丝·李奇曼
Cloris Leachman is...
比你重要多了
More important than you.
-我不是针对你  -对 没事 我知道
- It's not personal. - Uh, no, I know.
我就是
I'm just, um...
还挺期待跟贝乌拉聊一聊的
I was really looking forward to speaking with Beulah.
对 没错 我其实也特期待跟你聊聊
Oh, yeah, well, I mean, I could say the same about you.
我在《美联社》负责出版报道
I cover the publishing beat at the "AP,"
我一直在关注大家对《风骚女子》的讨论
and I have been following the chatter about "Minx."
这本新杂志
New magazine.
已经引起了出版市场的侧目 很不容易
Starting to make some noise. Not easy.
能够在这个市场
Well, I'm just grateful
占据一席之地 我很感激
to be part of the conversation, really.
那就让乔伊斯·普里格讲讲自己的故事吧
Well, let's dive into the story of Joyce Prigger.
好啊
Okay.
母权制第一次觉醒是什么时候
When did the matriarchy first awaken?
看来你做过家庭作业喔
You've done your research, I see.
职责所在
That's the job,
你也是记者 所以你肯定也懂
as you're aware, being a journalist yourself.
我故事跟千千万万的好故事一样 开始于
Well, I guess my story starts where every good story starts.
塞尼卡福尔斯大会是美国第一个妇女权利大会
塞尼卡福尔斯大会
Seneca Falls, 1848.
女性色情作家预言了一场性别战争
你真这么说了吗
Did you actually say that?
当然不是
Obviously not.
我说的是 我想开展一场
I said I wanted to start
关于女性压迫的对话
a conversation about female oppression.
我的观点被严重歪曲了
My point of view has been egregiously misrepresented.
好了 等等
Okay, okay, hold on.
当被问及《风骚女子》的读者受众时
"When pressed on 'Minx's' intended audience,
普里格毫不客气地鼓励13岁的女生
"Prigger cast a wide net, encouraging girls
去阅读她的杂志
as young as 13 to seek out her magazine"?
我的原话是 在我的成长过程中
I said that I wish I had access
要是有这样的杂志就好了
to this kind of material when I was coming of age.
在你成长过程中
Oh, you are coming of age.
-我才不信  -我们得解决这个事
Believe me. - We have to fix this.
我们得要求撤稿
We've gotta demand a retraction.
绝对不行 这篇报道已经火爆全国了
No way. This is a national story.
超过180家报纸进行了登载
It's been picked up by 180 papers
简直要赶上第二期发行时的阵势了
just as we have released issue two.
我们中大奖了
This is a jackpot.
还有更好的
Oh, this one's even better.
色情文学作家为暴力辩护
"Pornographer defends riot,
倡议青少年性觉醒
advocates for adolescent sexual awakening"?
乔伊斯 你就是个宝藏女孩啊
Joyce, you're a fucking gold mine!
我天
Oh, my God.
你是里卡多·蒙特斯·伊姿奎查吗
Are you Ricardo Montes Izquierda?
不是
No.
谢谢
Thank you.
这鞋也该算我的了吧
Don't they sort of belong to me by now?
借来的高跟鞋
There's no statute of limitations
从没有法定时效
on borrowed pumps.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那个手包我也是会来拿的 小姐
And I'm coming for that clutch, missy.
你确定不要留下来喝一杯吗
Are you sure you can't stay for a drink?
我倒是想 不过一会儿要起雾了
Well, I would, I just-- I want to hit the highway
我得抓紧上高速
before the smog rolls in.
要不这周你来办公室找我吧
Well, maybe you can come by the office this week.
我们都好想你
We all miss you.
我保证很快就去看你们
I promise I'm gonna stop by soon.
但这两天家里事太多
It's just been so crazy at the house
我和莱尼的关系有点怪怪的
and things with Lenny have been a little off.
我这几天 其实很需要你的陪伴
- I just-- I really could have used you the last few days.
人人都讨厌我 谢尔
It's-- everybody hates me, Shel.
一开始是杂志接受群嘲
First it was the magazine,
现在是我接受群嘲
but now I am the one being pilloried.
乔伊斯 你还记得没人出版你的杂志时
Joycey, when no one would publish your magazine,
你有多痛苦吗
do you remember how miserable you were?
太痛苦了 所有人都对我视而不见
Yeah, it's terrible to be ignored.
第一期杂志出版后
And then after the first issue came out
销量感人 你当时以为
and no one bought it, you felt like
世界末日要来了
it was the end of the world.
那是因为杂志是带着雷鸣
That's because it landed
降生到这个世界的
with a deafening thud.
严重冲击了旧秩序
It's a real shock to the system.
我只想说 如果每走一步都对你是个折磨
I'm just saying, if every step has been torture,
这不禁让我思考 你真的想办这个杂志吗
it makes me wonder, do you even want a magazine?
我当然想办杂志了 只是没想到
Of course I want a magazine. It's just it's harder
现实比预想中要难很多 仅此而已
than I thought it was gonna be, that's all.
好吧 世上之事大抵如此
Yeah, well, most things are.
哟 道尔顿家的 我喜欢他家的费南雪蛋糕
Ooh, Daltons. I love their financiers.
-有人暗恋你吧  -快走吧
Secret admirer? - Bye.
谢谢你跟我一起来
Well, thank you for joining me.
正好来亲眼看看
You know how much I love to see
这一本本杂志是怎么为咱们赚钱的
our profitable magazines in their natural environment.
啊 《裸体护士》
Ahh, "Naked Nurses."
利润率70% 多带劲儿
Ugh, 70%margin. Now that's sexy.
-《风骚女子》在哪儿  -不会吧
Where the hell is "Minx"? - Oh, no.
底袋钱金钱帝国皇冠上的宝石
Has the crown jewel of the Bottom Dollar empire
又不见了吗
gone missing yet again?
嘿 阿蒂
Hey, Artie!
我们不是说过这个事了吗 我的露屌杂志呢
I thought we'd been over this. Where's my dick mag?
-没了 他们全部拿走了  -被查了吧
- Gone. They took it all. - Seized?
-当然了 他们要查的  -并不是 是卖掉了
- Sure, that tracks. - No, sold.
我摆在书架上 两个小时内就被抢购一空
I put it on the stands, gone in two hours.
你得再多给我供点货
You gotta get me more.
没问题
No problem.
这么说吧 弗兰考
So get this, Franco.
在阳光明媚的洛杉矶一个叫乔伊斯·普利格的女人
Some broad right here in sunny LA, Joyce Prigger,
打算出版一本上面全都是裸男的杂志
is putting out a magazine full of naked guys
来帮助女性获得更多的满足感
to help the females feel more satisfied.
哈 你听我说 我打赌要是普利格女士
Ha! You know, I bet if Little Miss Prigger
有个真棒棒可以玩
had a real-life jolly stick to play with,
她就不会这么烦恼了
she would have saved herself the trouble.
我们刚在克利夫兰售罄了
We just sold out in Cleveland!
什么
What?
她把这个杂志命名为《风骚女子》
Well, she's calling it "Minx",
她还在上面刊登了
and she has filled it
她的所有关于女权主意的光辉言论
with all of her feminist mumbo jumbo.
你读了吗 南希
Are you reading this, Nancy?
你最好拜读一下 比利
You better believe it, Billy Boy.
伙计们 把你们的妞管好了
Fellas, keep a leash on your ladies.
千万不要让她们有任何宏大的想法
Don't want 'em getting any big ideas.
我想加薪
I want a raise.
这些自由主义者都是这个毛病
That's the thing about these libbers.
他们总是想着去修理一下压根就没任何毛病的东西
They wanna fix something that ain't broken.
要求既能上得厅堂
How hard is it to get your nails done
又能下得厨房这件事到底有多难
and cook a nice meal?
我们刚刚在维加斯售罄
We just sold out Vegas!
像乔伊斯· 普利格这样的女人 简直就是祸水
Chicks like Joyce Prigger, nothing but trouble.
但是我太清楚这种女人了
But I know the type.
一旦要是哪个不幸的家伙把她娶回家
Once some unlucky guy takes her off the market,
她就再也不会发声了
she'll shut her trap.
哦 要是我们的哪个忠实的听众
Oh, if any of our loyal listeners
愿意英勇的担起这个重任 你就是我们顶礼膜拜的英雄
wanna jump on that grenade, you'll be a hero to us all.
纽约
New York City!
抵制色情 抵制色情
Parks, not porn! Parks, not porn!
抵制色情
Parks, not porn!
朋友们 邻居们 妻子们 母亲们
Friends, neighbors, wives, mothers,
这场战争并非出自我们的意愿
we didn't ask for this war,
但是我向你们保证 我们已经准备好出征了
but I promise you, we're ready to fight it.
如果乔伊斯·普利格和她的那帮下流士兵
If Joyce Prigger and her soldiers of smut
放任这些杂志流入我们不谙世事的孩子们手中
wanna put their magazines into the hands of our children,
必须得先过了我们这一关
well, they're going to have to get through us first.
-嘿 里奇  -嘿
- Hey, Richie. - Hey.
里奇
"Richie,
恭喜你的第二期杂志成功出版 做得很棒
"congrats on a fabulous second issue.
我为我的艺术家们准备了一场沙龙
"Having a little salon for some of my artists
地点在我的山庄的房子里
"at my place in the hills.
可以把你的同事带过来
"Bring your colleagues.
想要和《风骚女子》的家人们共同庆祝 来自爱德华
Would love to celebrate with the whole 'Minx' team. Edward."
-咱们得去啊  -我没空
- We have to go. - I'm pretty busy.
-我觉得我就不  -你说什么
- I don't think I can make - What?
你之前见到他不是挺激动的吗
You were so excited to meet him.
哦 不 他是想把你给睡了
Oh, no. He tried to sleep with you.
你真和他睡了 还是你和他已经睡过两次了
You did sleep with him? You slept with him twice?
感觉好吗 还是很糟糕
It was good? It was bad.
-还是他厌母  -打住
- He hates his mother. - Stop.
我怯场了 可以吗
I bailed, okay?
我那次去了那里
I got there and it was
发现自惭形秽
way out of my league.
我这辈子都不可能和霍克尼一样
There's no chance I'm ever gonna be
挂在墙上光彩照人
up on a wall next to Hockney.
你知道吗 当年我迈出第一步的时候
You know, when I stepped on my first set,
我感觉自己压根就不配
I didn't feel like I belonged.
我甚至都不知道我怎么到那里的
I'm not even really sure how I got there.
摄影师看出来我很紧张
But the photographer could tell I was really nervous,
所以她就走到我跟前 跟我说
and so he walked over to me and he said,
你不会一直这么性感
"You're not gonna be hot forever.
现在把你腿上的短裤脱了
"Now take off those shorts
骑到那头大象身上
and get on that elephant and ride."
这行业简直了
Oh, this industry.
亲 你这么才华横溢
Babes, you're so talented.
你要做的就是闪闪发光 然后告诉所有人
You just need to shine bright and show everyone
你值得万众瞩日
how much you're worth.
再说了 也该让乔伊斯开心下
Plus, Joyce could use some fun.
我们可以好好尽兴一晚上
We could make a night of it.
好 好吧 我去
Okay, fine, fine,
但我可以想走就走
but I get to leave whenever I want.
你现在是这么说
Okay, you say that now,
但是我上次参加的山庄派对时
but last time I went to a party in the hills,
在那呆了一年 流连忘返
I stayed for a year.
之后就接连几起谋杀案
And then the murders started.
你一定会爱上那种感觉的
You're gonna love it.
你是说曼森连环谋杀案
The Manson murders?
不是那个
Not those!
图书馆 那个全世界我最
The library, one of my favorite places
-钟爱的地方  -她说得有道理
- in the entire world. - I mean, she has a point.
就连我都觉得《风骚女子》不该放在图书馆里
Even I don't think "Minx" should be in a library.
我从来没这么说过
I never said that.
好了 我来唱个反调
You know, just to play devil's advocate,
让大众熟知这些理念
who is to say it's the worst idea
一定就是件很糟糕的事吗
to bring these concepts to the common square?
如果你觉得大众能够在手持一本《费恩历险记》的同时
If you think people should be able to check out your magazine
还有眼光鉴赏你的杂志
while also getting a copy of "Huckleberry Finn,"
我觉得这才是你需要
I think that's an opinion you need to share
和世界分享的想法
with the whole world.
哦 那你一定爱听
Oh, yeah, you would love that.
不 我喜欢杂志大火大卖
No, I love selling magazines.
话说回来 你愿意上
And speaking of, would you be willing
《威利和弗兰考》的节目吗
to go on "Willy and Franco"?
可能会对销量有帮助
Pump up our numbers a little bit?
我考虑都不会考虑的
I wouldn't go anywhere near them.
他们简直就是原始人
They're Neanderthals.
拥有全国观众的原始人
Neanderthals with a national audience.
道格 我都收到恐吓信了
Doug, I am getting hate mail.
一沓一沓的
Bags and bags of it.
四字经 又是四字经
Four-letter word. Four-letter word.
五字经 死亡威胁
Five-letter word. Death threat.
哦 天呐 还有这个底袋钱杂志的
Oh, God, and this absolute chestnut
忠实脑残粉 诺曼
from Bottom Dollar's biggest fan, Norman.
色情杂志上的女人是用来看的 不该发出声音
"Women in pornography should be seen and not heard
当然也不该拥有属于自己的杂志
"and certainly should not be given their own magazine.
你就像那个邪恶的狐狸精小野洋子
"Like that vile temptress Yoko Ono,
在赤手空拳撼动美国的披头士
"you are single-handedly unraveling America's Beatles.
底袋钱出版商
Bottom Dollar Publications."
他把我们和披头士乐队相提并论
he thinks we're The Beatles.
-道格  -乔伊斯 我在这行
- Doug! - Joyce, I've been
摸爬滚打已经很久了 你也知道
in this business a Iong time, and as you know,
这不会永远受人待见
it is not always a popular one.
我想给你看点特别的
I want to show you something special.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
我最喜欢的几封情书
A few of my favorite love letters.
要是我有一台时光机 我会穿越回1933年
"If I had a time machine, I'd go back to 1933
在你还在襁褓中的时候 就把你杀死 如果时间允许的话
"and kill you as a toddler, then, time permitting,
我还会去到德国 杀了希特勒
I'd go to Germany and I'd kill Hitler."
-这太变态了  -你得这么想 有人肯下功夫
That is horrible. - No, if somebody is willing
给你写信 意味着你戳到了他们痛处
to write you a letter, that means you got them.
意味着你有影响力
That means that you matter.
你说的这些人和受虐狂有什么两样
What you're describing is masochism.
你没明白我的意思 你压根就不用鸟这些人
No, what I'm describing is not giving a shit.
你就应该有这种心态
You should try that sometime.
-你还挺喜欢这个 对吗  -对啊
- Really enjoying this, huh? - I am.
如果你承认我是对的
The only way this could be any better
那这一刻的感觉就更加锦上添花了
is you admitting that I was right.
说得好像你造有预感一样
Like you knew any of this was gonna happen.
我可是有第六感的
Hey, I had a hunch.
你明明是闭着眼睛投飞镖
You were blindly throwing darts
指望能命中
praying one would hit.
没想到还真命中了
And one did,
就射在我们的守护神的屁股上
right in the ass of our patron saint,
乔伊斯·普利格
Joyce Prigger, huh?
当然了 如果她能做得长久
Sure, if she holds.
你这是把宝都押在了
You've hitched your wagon to a star
一颗随时有可能爆炸的明星上
that's about to supernova out of existence.
没事
Nah, I'm good.
我考虑把下次的印刷量
I'm thinking of upping our next print run
增加到一百万
to a cool million.
-为什么不是两百万  -看来你胃口也不小嘛
Why not two? - Now she's ready to dance.
为什么不是两百万
Why not two?
就祈祷我们没站在泰坦尼克号的甲板上吧
Just hope it's not on the deck of the "Titanic."
那些人尽管身处绝境
Hey, those people were in a bad situation,
但却尽全力做到了最好
and they made the best of it.
但是他们最后不是都死了
And then they all died.
布鲁尔被誉为全国顶尖脑外科医生
瓦萨学院校友领导国际饥荒救济工作
嘿 你怎么过来了
Hey. What're you doing here--
别 别说话
No, don't talk.
-早上好  -早上好
- Morning. - Good morning.
-好开心  -对啊 很开心
- That was fun. - Yes, it was.
我都忘了我们以前有多契合
I forgot how good we are at this.
昨晚好像更契合了
That was a little better.
对吗
Right?
看来你真的读了《激情爱爱》
Well, you did read "Aphrodesia."
过来
Come here.
我真希望一整天都躲在你怀里
I wish I could just hide out here all day.
当然可以了 我会帮你接电话
You can. I'll field your calls.
打得那些口无遮拦的家伙满地找牙
Beat away all those assholes running their mouths.
这恐怕有点晚了
God, it's a bit late for that.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
没有不能修复的形象
Nobody's image is beyond repair.
泰迪·肯尼迪当年的河边惨案
Teddy Kennedy is three years removed
过去三年了
from leaving a body in an estuary,
但觉得他可以当总统的人大有人在
and he's still a viable presidential candidate.
这么类比不太恰当吧 但是
Not my favorite analogy, but...
玛莎葡萄园岛现在听起来确实令人心驰神往
Martha's Vineyard does sound very appealing right now.
但是你自己知道你不能在这么躲下去了
But you know you shouldn't be hiding.
你应该反击
You should fight back.
丘吉尔说过 在真相还没有为人所知之前
Churchill said that, "A lie gets halfway around the world
流言蜚语早就不胫而走了
before the truth puts its pants on."
道格对真相不感兴趣
Doug's not interested in the truth.
但你的生意搭档的确是个
Well, you did get in business with a man
对严肃杂志出版一无所知的人
who doesn't know a thing about publishing a real magazine.
你需要的是一个有相关媒体人脉的出版商
You deserve a publisher who has the right media contacts,
要了解主要市场
someone who understands major markets,
找得到真正的出版商
who has relationships with advertisers,
他知道秋季是杂志畅销的季节
who knows that fall issues are the biggest
而一月份是淡季
and January's a wash.
听起来你好像已经有人选了
It sounds like you have someone in mind.
你没和对的人上床
It's not your fault that you got into bed
这并不是你的错
with the wrong guy.
你只是太渴望肯定了 所以才和一个
You were just so desperate for a yes
不知道你是谁 也不知道你想要什么的人
that you went with someone who doesn't know a thing
绑在一起
about who you are and what you want to do.
但如果我的出版商是像你这样的人
But if someone like you were my publisher...
说到这个
Well, now that you mention it,
其实我一直想采取行动
I have been looking to make a move.
《小伙子》杂志的眼界太窄了
"Lad" magazine is very limiting,
他们看不到我的潜力
and they don't see my potential.
说说看 格伦
Spit it out, Glenn.
莉莉奶奶留给我一笔小额信托
I've been sitting on a modest trust from Nana Lily.
-什么时候开始的  -她死后
- Since when? - Since she died.
-1969年吗  -是的
- In 1969? - Yes.
足够开店了
And it's enough to set up shop.
《风骚女子》就是我们的旗舰店名
"Minx" as our flagship title,
你当我们迷人的主编
and you as our glamorous editor in chief,
我就是温文尔雅的出版商
and me, our debonair publisher.
简直亮瞎眼
Look out, world.
你有这些钱 两年前干嘛去了
Where was this money two years ago?
我当时不想花在还没证实的事情上
Well, I didn't wanna blow it on something unproven.
我
Me.
你不想花在我身上
You didn't want to blow it on me.
我的天
Oh, my God.
但现在所有人都在谈论我的杂志
But now that everyone is talking about my magazine,
你就突然想给我投资了吗
now, suddenly, you wanna invest?
就你会误解我的意思
Only you can turn this into something nefarious.
我是想帮忙
I'm-- I'm trying to help.
帮帮你自己吧
Help yourself!
有什么好笑的
What is so funny?
我明白了 你想偷走我的杂志
I realized that you trying to steal my magazine--
这就是你做过最有野心的事情了
that is the most ambitious thing you've ever done.
宝贝 你看起来真帅
Ooh, you look hot, babe.
外面都32度了 怎么大家都穿成这样
It's, like, 91 degrees. Why do people dress like this?
所有人都会想找你搭讪的
Everyone's gonna wanna talk to you,
而我会一直站在你身边
and I'll be right by your side.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他们看起来真的都太帅了
Everyone is so staggeringly handsome, I kid you not.
他们真好看
They're so cute.
你先混个脸熟 我去拿点饮料
Hey, you mingle. I'll go grab us some drinks.
混个脸熟
Mingle?
那是
Is that--
我操
Motherfuck.
怎么回事 那小妞还来吗
What's happening here? This chick gonna show?
是的 她会来的
Oh, yeah, yeah. No, she's gonna come.
我和她确认了三次 她还在开车
I triple confirmed with her. She's just driving.
女人嘛
You know, women.
要加奶油和两块糖哦 小甜心
Cream and two sugars, sugar.
但如果她不来 我很乐意替她上场
But if she doesn't show, I'll be happy to step in.
相信我 我有一万个故事可以讲
I got a-- I got a million stories, believe me.
她会的那些都是我教的
I taught her everything she knows.
我可幽默了
I'm a lot of fun.
话筒在哪
Where's the mic?
去吧
Go. Go.
你真的觉得我们40年后还会坐在这
You really think we're gonna be sitting here
戈尔迪·霍恩 美国著名演员 歌手
讨论戈尔迪·霍恩吗
in 40 years talking about Goldie Hawn?
不仅是她 还有她的孩子 她会建立一个帝国的
Not just her, her children. She's going to start an empire.
我可不想活在这种世界里
That's not a world I want to live in.
抱歉 你们有人开了一辆
Hi, sorry, um, do any of you happen to drive
绿白相间的皮卡吗
a green and white pickup?
这是那辆绿白相间的皮卡的钥匙吗
Is that to a green and white pickup?
蓝色塞利卡 想来一口吗
Blue Celica. You want?
听说我堵了你的车
I hear I'm holding you hostage.
非常抱歉
Dreadfully sorry.
-霍克尼先生  -我总是最后一个来的
Mr. Hockney. - I'm always the last one here.
堵住别人的车
End up trapping everybody else.
给我的压力可真大啊
That's the burden of my life.
介绍下你自己吧
And tell me who you are, then.
我以前认识爱德的派对上的每个人
I used to know everybody at Ed's parties,
不过看来我被潮流所遗弃了
but seems like this town is just moving on without me.
我只是个无名之辈
Oh, well, I'm a nobody.
我是里奇 我给《风骚女子》摄影
I'm Richie. I shoot for "Minx."
-是一本杂志  -太牛了
- It's a magazine that-- - Oh, no, brilliant.
我很喜欢《风骚女子》
I love "Minx."
尤其第二期 可是顶尖的啊
That second issue-- yeah, that was tops.
-你读过吗  -是啊
Oh, you've read it? - Yeah, well,
我们只能拍出折磨人的姿势
all we get are these tortured physique poses.
而木板路上的健美男子
Beefcakes on the boardwalk which, uh,
神情也到位 多好啊
with the right mood, I mean, why not?
不过你们展示了真正的男性欲望
But you're giving us actual male desire.
真了不起
That's really something.
谢谢你
Thank you.
说起来挺有意思 毕竟大家都在痛骂我们
It's funny 'cause people have been ripping us to shreds, so--
那就是成为佼佼者的代价吧
That's the price of being a pioneer, I suppose.
被大多数人误解
Misunderstood by most.
你们会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
我们回来了
And we're back!
有一本大热的新杂志受到关注
Well, there is a hot new magazine on the stands,
大家对此好像都持不同的观点
and everyone seems to have an opinion about it.
我们有幸请到了《风骚女子》的幕后大佬
We're lucky enough to have the brains behind "Minx."
-她可是处在风口浪尖啊  -那你倒说对了
It's a real lightning rod. - You got the rod part right.
热烈欢迎
Please welcome
《风骚女子》的女编辑 乔伊斯·普里格
the lady editor of "Minx," Joyce Prigger.
叫我编辑就行了 很高兴来此做客
Just editor. Happy to be here.
听众们 告诉你们一个可能让人惊讶的消息
Listeners, this may surprise you,
乔伊斯可是个大美女哦
but Joyce is quite the looker.
你听到女权这两个字 就觉得
You hear "feminist" and you think...
真有意思 你们俩和我料想的一模一样
That's funny, you both look exactly like I imagined.
哇哦
Whoa!
那么乔伊斯 你为什么讨厌男人
So, Joyce, why do you hate men?
慢着 她可不讨厌男人
Whoa, whoa, whoa, she doesn't hate men.
你看过她的杂志了吗 她可爱我们了
You check out her mag? She loves us.
可能不是我们
Eh, maybe not us,
只是那个能讨她欢心的小家伙
but a little part that tickles her fancy.
打断一下 我并不讨厌男人
To interject, I don't hate men at all.
但对于男人 有一件事我觉得好奇
But one thing I find curious about them
他们问女人一个问题后
is when they ask a woman a question
居然还不让她回答
and then don't let her answer it.
糟糕 我们好像
Oh, no, I think we ticked her off
惹她生气了 威利
right out of the gate, Willy.
我们只是闹着玩呢
Oh, we're just messing around.
我们可不想惹你
There's no reason to get your nose out of joint.
我喜欢的另一件事是 男人想告诉我
Another thing I love is when men try to tell me
我应该对事情抱有怎样的感想
how I should be feeling.
《风骚女子》可不是关于厌男的
"Minx" is not about hating men.
是关于赋权女性的
It's about empowering women.
吓到你了吗 威利
Does that scare you, Willy?
当然不怕
Of course not.
是啊 像我这样的小女子
Right, cause how could little ol me
怎么会吓到你这种猛男呢
scare a big man like you?
不过佛朗哥应该感到害怕
Franco, on the other hand, should be terrified.
南希 你没权利碰这些
Nancy, you don't have those privileges.
看 这才是我杂志的宗旨
See, now that is what my magazine is all about.
男人们已经独裁很久了
Men have had their finger on the button for a long time.
这是我的按钮 她知道规矩的
Well, that's my button, and she knows the rules.
我们不是想夺走你按按钮的权利 威利
We're not trying to take your button away, Willy.
女人们只是想碰一下按钮
Women just want access to the button,
那也不行的话 我们想要自己的按钮
or, failing that, we want our own button,
和你那个一样吵闹又烦人的
one as loud and obnoxious as yours.
你这头起的可真不错啊
Oh, you're just off to a great start, toots.
我明白了
I get it. I get it. I do.
男人们按耐不住了
一个女性色情摄影师
The thought of a female pornographer--
让人很不舒服
that makes people pretty uncomfortable.
让我不舒服 不过我还是要这么做
It made me uncomfortable, but I'm doing it anyway.
而且你们无论做什么
And there is nothing that you can do to co-opt it
也不会让我打消念头 也夺不走
or diminish it or take that away from me.
威尔 你看色情片吧
Will, you look at porn, right?
这是我和我的 看啊
That's between me and my-- yes.
佛朗哥 我都不用问你了
Franco, I don't even need to ask.
男人的欲望是值得庆祝的
Male desire is celebrated.
甚至有一整个行业为其服务
There is an entire industry built on servicing it.
那为什么女性的欲望有所不同
Why should female desire be any different?
我们性器官的神经末梢比你们多
We got more nerve endings in our sex organs than you do.
不 绝对不许听
No. Absolutely not!
像你们这样的男人真的很擅长约束女人
Men like you are really good at limiting women's options.
现在也许 只是也许 你们在担心
Now maybe, just maybe, you guys are worried
我的杂志能为她们提供 你们无法提供的东西
that my magazine can offer them something that you can't.
不过有一件事我很确定 旺达·威尔克森
One thing I'm certain of is that Wanda Wilkerson
能在卧室得到满足
is satisfied in the bedroom department.
-那你呢  -从来没有抱怨过
Are you, though? - Never had a single complaint.
我相信你们的婚姻
And I'm sure that your marriages
都建立在开放和沟通的基础上
are built on openness and communication.
-其实我单身  -我还挺惊讶
- Actually, I'm single. - Shocker.
但作为一个女人 让我告诉你一个小秘密
But as a woman, let me let you in on a little secret.
她告诉你的和实际情况
What she tells you and what's really happening
可能不是一回事
may not be the same thing.
我认识一个已婚16年的女人
I happen to know a woman who's been married
有三个孩子 完美的生活
for 16 years-- three kids, perfect life.
但她的丈夫一直没能给她
But her husband has never been able to give her
最完整的性爱体验
the fullest experience of lovemaking.
她从没一句怨言
She has never said a peep about it,
所以他一直瞎嚯嚯 以为自己让她爽到了
so he keeps flying blind thinking he's pleasuring her.
但我相信
But I'm sure that things
你和旺达之间是不同的
between you and Wanda are different.
休息后我们可以给她打个电话
We could give her a call after the break.
听听她对这个故事的看法
Hear her side of the story.
好主意 南希
Great idea, Nancy.
买一个白金的要多少钱
How much to get one of these in platinum?
-到处都售罄了  -消息传得很快
We sold out everywhere. - Word travels fast.
迪克·卡维特的经纪人
Dick Cavett's talent booker told me
电话询问乔伊斯是否有空时告诉我的
when she called to check Joyce's availability.
不是吧 “迪克·卡维特秀”吗
No. "The Dick Cavett Show"?
纽约的那个吗
In New York fuckin' City?
你的消息怎么会比我的好
How is your news better than my news?
真烦人 我可是有好消息的
This is annoying. I had great news.
你会克服的
You'll get over it.
好吧 我需要听到你亲口说
All right, I need to hear it.
-真的吗  -是啊 我可是个小人
- Seriously? - Yeah, I'm a petty man.
我想听
I want to hear it.
好吧 我来给你铺垫下
All right, maybe I'll make it easier for you.
你说的也对
You were right too.
我不负责任 我太过自负
I was irresponsible, I was in over my head, I
我有点疯了
I went a little nuts.
然后我就走运了
And then I got lucky.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有呢
And?
你是对的
You were right.
阴茎和原始版本完全不成比例
The penis is completely out of proportion to the original.
-是的 这是件大事  -是的 我们知道
- Yeah, it was a whole thing. - Yes, we know.
我希望大家没别的地方去
I hope no one's got anywhere to be,
因为我刚挡了五个人的去路
because I just blocked in about five people.
现在他们有理由留下来了
Well, now they have a reason to stay.
各位 这是乔伊斯
Hey, everyone, this is Joyce.
《风骚女子》后的风骚女子
The minx behind "Minx."
上帝保佑丁丁女王
God save the queen of dicks.